Register to The Quincy Porter Papers
Yale University Music Library
- Correspondence, Series I
  - Yale Papers, I.I
    - Bozyan, H. Frank (Box 13, Folder 168)
      No year Jul 15 -- autograph letter signed
    - Brieff, Frank (Box 13, Folder 168)
    - Buck, Norman S. (Box 13, Folder 168)
      1959 -- 2 autograph letters signed
      1947-1959 -- 2 typed letters signed
      1947 Feb 11 -- typed letter (carbon) from Quincy Porter to above
    - Calhoun, Robert L. (Box 13, Folder 168)
      1966 Sep 18 -- typed letter signed
    - Calleo, David P. (Box 13, Folder 168)
      1965 Dec 3 -- typed letter signed
    - Cannon, Beekman
      See: New Haven Symphony; general correspondence
    - Carroll, Richard C. (Box 13, Folder 168)
      1961 May 24 -- typed letter signed (carbon) [to Ian Underwood]
    - [Chamier, Anthony ?] (Box 13, Folder 168)
    - Chauncey, Henry, Jr. (Box 13, Folder 168)
      1964 Jul 22 -- typed letter signed
    - Clare Scholarship Committee (Box 13, Folder 168)
    - Clark, R. Inslee (Box 13, Folder 168)
    - Closson, Henry (Heinie) (Box 13, Folder 168)
      1958 Apr 21 -- typed letter signed
    - Coeller, Mary M. (Box 13, Folder 168)
      1964 Jul 8 -- typed letter signed
    - Coffin, William Sloane (Box 13, Folder 168)
      1965 May 11 -- typed letter signed
    - Crosby, Sumner (Box 13, Folder 168)
      1959 Jan 26 -- typed letter (carbon) from Quincy Porter to above
    - Davenny, Ward (Box 13, Folder 168)
      1961 May 29 -- autograph letter signed [to John Contiguglia]
    - Davidson, Eugene A. (Box 13, Folder 168)
      1958 Jul 7 -- rough copy from Quincy Porter to above
    - Davis, Hallie Flanagan (Box 13, Folder 168)
      1958 Apr 16 -- autograph letter signed
    - De Loache, Benjamin
    - Donovan, Richard (Box 13, Folder 169)
      1938; 1961; No date -- 4 autograph letters signed (1-scrapbook)
      1938-1942 -- 4 typed letters signed
      1939 Apr 18 -- typed letter (copy)
      1939 Mar 20 -- card
    - Dunham, William (Box 13, Folder 169)
      1958 Apr 17 -- autograph letter signed
    - Foard, Archie (Box 13, Folder 169)
    - Forman, Charles W. (Box 13, Folder 169)
      1962 Aug 9 -- typed letter (carbon) from Quincy Porter to above
    - Forte, Allen (Box 13, Folder 169)
      1960-1961 -- 2 typed letters signed (1-scrapbook) [one to Ward Davenny]
    - French, Richard F.
      See: Harvard University; Associated Music Publishers, Inc.
    - Frost, Robert [to Gordon ?] (Box 13, Folder 169)
      1959 Feb 25 -- typed letter signed
      1960 Sep 16 -- typed letter (carbon) from Quincy Porter to above
    - Fulton, John F. (Box 13, Folder 169)
      1959 Oct 8 -- typed letter signed
    - Furniss, S.S. (Box 13, Folder 169)
      1940; 1953 -- 2 typed letters signed
    - Gabriel, Robert T. (Box 13, Folder 170)
    - Garside, Charles (Box 13, Folder 170)
      1958 Apr 22 -- typed letter signed
    - Garside, Charles, Jr. (Box 13, Folder 170)
      1961 Mar 2 -- typed letter (carbon) from Quincy Porter to above
    - Griswold, Richard W. (Box 13, Folder 170)
      1958 Apr 18 -- autograph letter signed
    - Grumman, Ellsworth (Box 13, Folder 170)
      1931; 1938 -- 2 autograph letters signed (1-scrapbook)
    - Guptil, Constance (Box 13, Folder 170)
      1964 Feb 4 -- typed letter signed from Quincy Porter to above
    - Haight, Gordon S. (Box 13, Folder 170)
      1958 Apr 10 -- autograph letter signed
    - Hanway, William A. (Box 13, Folder 170)
      1958 Apr 25 -- typed letter signed
    - Hehre, Josephine C. (Box 13, Folder 170)
      1959 Dec 8 -- autograph letter signed
    - Henning, B.D. ("Duke") (Box 13, Folder 170)
      1958 Apr ? -- autograph letter signed
    - Henry Fund (Box 13, Folder 170)
      1959 Jan 26 -- 2 typed letters (carbon) from Quincy Porter to above
    - Hersey, John (Box 13, Folder 170)
      1965 Sep 23 -- autograph letter signed
    - Hindemith, Gertrude and Paul (Box 13, Folder 170)
      See also: Lois Porter's correspondence
    - Holden, Reuben A. (Box 13, Folder 170)
      1963; No date -- 2 autograph letters signed
      1958 Nov 21 -- typed letter signed
      1958 Oct 15 -- typed letter (carbon) from Quincy Porter to above
    - Holden, Mr. and Mrs. Reuben A. (Box 13, Folder 170)
      1965 Apr 11 -- autograph letter signed
    - Howe, Arthur, Jr. (Box 13, Folder 170)
      1958 Oct 21 -- typed letter (carbon) from Quincy Porter to above
    - Hutchins, Margaret [cousin] (Box 13, Folder 170)
    - Jackson, Rose (Box 13, Folder 171)
    - Johnson, Anita (Box 13, Folder 171)
      1949 Aug 12 -- typed letter signed
    - Kirkpatrick, Ralph
      See: Century Association; Yaddo; general correspondence
    - Kunkel, John C. (Box 13, Folder 171)
      1959 Jun 16 -- typed letter signed
      1959 Jun 18 -- typed letter (carbon) from Quincy Porter [secretary] to above
    - Lee, Richard C. (Box 13, Folder 171)
      1950 Jun 13 -- typed letter signed
    - Lewin, Frank
      See: general correspondence; Catgut Acoustical Society
    - Lewis, Robert J. (Box 13, Folder 171)
    - Liebert, Fritz (Box 13, Folder 171)
    - Loeffler, Alfred Thorpe (Box 13, Folder 171)
      1958 Apr 21 -- autograph letter signed
    - Lohmann, Carl A. (Box 13, Folder 171)
      1946 -- 2 typed letters signed (1-scrapbook)
    - Lovett, Sidney (Box 13, Folder 171)
      1958 Jul 1 -- typed letter signed
      See also: general correspondence
    - MacLean, Burton A. (Box 13, Folder 171)
      1958 Oct 7 -- autograph letter signed
      1958 Dec 1 -- typed letter signed
    - Macmillan, Eva Adams (Box 13, Folder 171)
      1958 May 1 -- typed letter signed
    - McMullan, Frank (Box 13, Folder 171)
      1954 Feb 24 -- autograph letter signed
    - Martino, Donald (Box 13, Folder 171)
      1961 Jan 13 -- typed letter (carbon) from Quincy Porter to above
    - Martz, Louis (Box 13, Folder 171)
      1960 Mar 24 -- typed letter (carbon) from Quincy Porter to above
    - Maurer, Marion E. (Box 13, Folder 171)
    - Moe, Henry Allen (Box 13, Folder 171)
      1958 Apr 15 -- typed letter signed
    - Moore, Douglas (Box 13, Folder 171)
    - Morris, Raymond P. (Box 13, Folder 171)
      1957 Mar 22 -- typed letter signed
    - Nagel, Anne R. (Box 13, Folder 172)
      1964 Jul 23 -- typed letter signed
    - Nangle, Ben (Box 13, Folder 172)
      1964-1965 -- 2 autograph letters signed
      1964 Jul 7 -- typed letter signed
    - Noss, Luther (Box 13, Folder 172)
      1951-1958 -- 2 autograph letters signed
    - Noss, Osea (Box 13, Folder 172)
    - Notestein, Wallace (Box 13, Folder 172)
    - Osborn, James M. (Box 13, Folder 172)
      1958 Nov 20 -- autograph letter signed
      1959 Jul 22 -- typed letter signed
      1959 Jul 15 -- card
    - Parisot, Aldo (Box 13, Folder 172)
      1966 Aug 3 -- typed letter signed from Quincy Porter to above
    - Peterkin, DeWitt, Jr. (Box 13, Folder 172)
      1958 May 7 -- typed letter signed
    - Peyre, Henri (Box 13, Folder 172)
      [1953 Apr] -- card
    - Pforzheimer, Walter L. (Box 13, Folder 172)
      1962 Apr 6 -- typed letter signed
      1962 Apr 10 -- typed letter (carbon) from Quincy Porter to above
    - Porter, Robert (Box 13, Folder 172)
      1965 Apr 24 -- typed letter signed (copy) from Quincy Porter to above
    - Root, Charles D., Jr. (Box 14, Folder 173)
    - Rostow, Gene and Edna (Box 14, Folder 173)
      [1958 Apr] -- autograph letter signed
    - Sandback, Helen K. (Box 14, Folder 173)
      1958; No year -- 2 typed letters signed
      1959 Jul 8 -- typed letter
      No year Dec 16 -- card
      1959 Jul 10 -- typed letter (carbon) from Quincy Porter to above
    - Schuman, William (Box 14, Folder 173)
      1958 May 5 -- typed letter signed
    - Sewall, Richard (Box 14, Folder 173)
      1965 May 7 -- 2 typed letters (carbon) from Quincy Porter to above
    - Seymour, Charles (Box 14, Folder 173)
      1946 May 16 -- typed letter signed (scrapbook)
      1946 May 19 -- typed letter (copy-scrapbook) from Quincy Porter to above
    - Shepard, Brooks (Box 14, Folder 173)
      1958-1965 -- 3 autograph letters signed
      1965 Jan 8 -- typed letter signed from Quincy Porter to above
      1960 Oct 13 -- typed letter (carbon) from Quincy Porter to above
    - Simon, Roger H. (Box 14, Folder 173)
      1965 Apr 28 -- autograph letter signed
    - Simonds, Bruce (Box 14, Folder 173)
      1946; 1952 -- 2 typed letters signed (1-scrapbook)
    - Simonds, Rosalind (Mrs. Bruce) (Box 14, Folder 173)
    - Smith, David Stanley (Box 14, Folder 173)
      1946 Jun 2 -- autograph letter signed (scrapbook)
    - Stern, Blake
    - Stuck, Cynthia (Box 14, Folder 174)
      1958 May 7 -- autograph letter signed
    - Sweet, Gordon (Box 14, Folder 174)
    - Thorne, Oakleigh, Jr. (Box 14, Folder 174)
    - Tyler, Morris (Box 14, Folder 174)
      1958 Apr 20 -- autograph letter signed
    - Vaill, George D. (Box 14, Folder 174)
      1947-1958 -- 2 typed letters signed
    - Waith, Eugene M. (Box 14, Folder 174)
      1960 Jul 25 -- autograph letter signed
      1959-1960 -- 3 typed letters signed
      1959 -- 2 typed letters (carbon) from Quincy Porter to above
    - Watson, Bill (Box 14, Folder 174)
      1959 Mar 12 -- autograph letter signed
    - Weber, Victor B., II (Box 14, Folder 174)
    - Weiss, Paul (Box 14, Folder 174)
    - Welles, C. Bradford (Box 14, Folder 174)
      1959 -- 3 typed letters signed
    - Welles, Tom (Box 14, Folder 174)
      1959 Feb 2 -- typed letter (carbon) from Quincy Porter to above
    - Wiggin, Frederick H. (Box 14, Folder 174)
    - Wilson, Keith (Box 14, Folder 175)
      1958-1960 -- 2 typed letters signed
    - Wittnenborn, Dick (Box 14, Folder 175)
      1947 Feb 19 -- typed letter
    - Wolfers, Arnold (Box 14, Folder 175)
    - Wyner, Yehudi (Box 14, Folder 175)
      1962 May 15 -- autograph letter signed
    - Yale University (certificates of appointment) (Box 14, Folder 175)
      1946-1960 -- 6 typed letters signed
    - Yale University. Band (Box 14, Folder 175)
      1958 Nov 4 -- typed letter signed
      2 pamphlets
    - Yale University. Placement Bureau (Box 14, Folder 175)
      1963 Apr 1 -- typed letter (carbon) from Quincy Porter to above
    - Yale University Press (Box 14, Folder 175)
      1960 Mar 24 -- memo
    - [Don ?] (Box 14, Folder 175)
      [1960] -- autograph letter signed
    - Unidentifiable (Box 14, Folder 175)
      1958 Jul 11 -- typed letter signed
    - Unidentifiable ["Froggy"] (Box 14, Folder 175)
      1960 Nov 28 -- telegram
    - Miscellaneous (Box 14, Folder 176)
      10 student recommendations, no address indicated
      1958-1965 -- 3 news releases
      1958-1962 -- 3 printed material
      1959 Jun 7 -- 1 prayer, Yale Baccalaureate
      1965 Nov 15 -- 1 program, Hersey installation dinner
    - Miscellaneous (Box 14, Folder 177)
      1959 Mar 17 -- 1 printed welcome to class of 1962
      1965-1966 -- 3 lists
      1 photograph sheet
      1965 Apr 17 -- 1 Pierson newspaper
    - Questions and answers for WYBC program; introductory remarks for special guests at Pierson dinners (Box 14, Folder 178)
    - Remarks from fellows' and students' dinners at Pierson (Box 14, Folder 179)
    - Blueprint, Pierson College snack bar (Box 14, Folder 180)
  - Early Correspondence With Family, I.J
    - Letters written while studying with Herbert Dittler (Box 15, Folder 181)
      1916 Jul -- 8 autograph letters signed
    - While in armed services (Box 15, Folder 182)
      1918 Jun-Oct -- 34 (mostly autograph letters signed)
    - While living in Cleveland (Box 15, Folder 183)
      1925 -- 2 typed letters signed
    - Paris years (Box 15, Folder 184-185)
      1929 May -- 3 autograph letters signed from family to Quincy Porter
      1928-1930 -- 325 pages of letters from Quincy Porter to family, in journal form
      1930-1931 -- 53 pages of letters from Quincy Porter to family, in journal form
    - From Quincy Porter to family (Box 15, Folder 186)
      1928-1931 -- 34 loose letters
      1928-1930 -- 4 cards
      1929 -- 2 telegrams
    - Typewritten excerpts about Porter's works, taken from French magazines and newspapers (Box 15, Folder 186)
  - Lois Porter's Correspondence, I.K
    (all to Lois Porter)
    - From Members of the Porter Family, I.K.1
      - Poems written by Porter family members (Box 16, Folder 187)
        No date -- 1 set
      - Porter, Delia Lyman [mother-in-law] (Box 16, Folder 187)
        3 autograph letters signed
      - Porter, Frank Chamberlin [father-in-law] (Box 16, Folder 187)
        1926-1944 -- 2 autograph letters signed
      - Porter, Quincy (Box 16, Folder 187)
        1926, Jun-Jul -- 13 autograph letters signed
    - General, I.K.2
      - American Composers Alliance (Box 16, Folder 188)
        1973 Aug 23 -- typed letter signed
      - Ames, Elizabeth (Box 16, Folder 188)
        1937 Jan 19 -- typed letter signed
      - Association of American Colleges (Box 16, Folder 188)
        1945 Apr 2 -- typed letter signed
      - Baisley, Robert W. (Box 16, Folder 188)
        1968 Feb 6 -- typed letter signed
      - Belvin Mills Publishing Corp. (Box 16, Folder 188)
        1972 Nov 10 -- typed letter signed
      - Blachman, Lucy (Box 16, Folder 188)
        1975 Sep 11 -- autograph letter signed
      - Boatwright family (Box 16, Folder 188)
        1957 Sep 4 -- card
      - Boston Public Library (Box 16, Folder 188)
        1945 Apr 11 -- typed letter signed
      - Century Association (Box 16, Folder 188)
        1967 Jun 2 -- typed letter signed
      - Contiguglia, Richard (Box 16, Folder 188)
        1967 Sep 23 -- autograph letter signed
        1968 Jan 17 -- typed letter signed
      - Cullen, Paula C. (Box 16, Folder 188)
        1964 Jul 29 -- typed letter signed
      - Curtis, Lewis P. (Box 16, Folder 188)
        1966 Nov 27 -- typed letter signed
      - D'Arms, Crit (Mrs. Edward F.) (Box 16, Folder 188)
        No year Aug 9 -- autograph letter signed
      - Doktor, Paul (Box 16, Folder 188)
        1959 May 3 -- card
      - Donaldson, Hildegarde (Box 16, Folder 188)
      - Edmunds, John (Box 16, Folder 188)
        1964 May 6 -- autograph letter signed
      - English, Katharine D. (Box 16, Folder 188)
        1951 May 3 -- autograph letter signed (scrapbook)
      - Fiduciary Trust Co. [to the H.W. Gray Company] (Box 16, Folder 188)
        1967 Oct 31 -- typed letter (carbon)
      - French, Bob (Box 16, Folder 188)
        1951 May 7 -- autograph letter signed (scrapbook)
      - H.W. Gray Company (Box 16, Folder 188)
        1971 Apr 1 -- typed letter signed
      - Hersey, Barbara (Box 16, Folder 188)
        1965 Jun 13 -- autograph letter signed
      - Hersey, John (Box 16, Folder 188)
        1967-1968 -- 3 autograph letters signed
      - [Hindemith, Gertrude ?] (Box 16, Folder 188)
        No year Feb 20 -- typed letter signed (scrapbook)
      - Howells, Dorothy Bryce (Box 16, Folder 188)
      - Morton J. Loeb Dental Clinic, Inc. (Box 16, Folder 188)
        1967 Apr 21 -- typed letter signed
      - Luskin, Leo S. (Box 16, Folder 188)
        1967 kor 3 -- typed letter signed
      - Mauceri, John (Box 16, Folder 189)
        1967 Oct 17 -- autograph letter signed
      - Moore, Emily (Box 16, Folder 189)
      - Northrup, Christine J. (Box 16, Folder 189)
        1950 Dec 7 -- autograph letter signed
      - Potter, Harrison (Box 16, Folder 189)
        1945 Mar 30 -- autograph letter signed
      - Rigby, John M. (Box 16, Folder 189)
        1951 May 8 -- typed letter signed (scrapbook)
      - Rogers, Dolly (Box 16, Folder 189)
        No year Jun 11 -- autograph letter signed
      - Schorer, Mark (Box 16, Folder 189)
        1958 Mar 10 -- typed letter signed
      - Second National Bank of New Haven, for the New Haven Foundation (Box 16, Folder 189)
      - Tolman, Mary H. (Box 16, Folder 189)
        1944 Dec 6 -- typed letter signed
      - Vassar College (Box 16, Folder 189)
        1938 Mar 23 -- typed letter signed (scrapbook)
      - Vassar College (Box 16, Folder 189)
        1933 Mar 25 -- 1 contract
      - Venable, Ruth (Box 16, Folder 189)
        1966 Mar 20 -- autograph letter signed
      - Williams, Charlotte D. (Box 16, Folder 189)
        1931 Feb 19 -- autograph letter signed
      - Frances ? (Box 16, Folder 189)
        1944 May 12 -- card
      - Hans ? (Box 16, Folder 189)
        1953 Mar 25 -- autograph letter signed
      - Contributions to the Quincy Porter Fund (Box 16, Folder 189)
        1 list
    - Letters in Response to Quincy Porter's Death, I.K.3
      - Altschul, Frank (Box 16, Folder 190)
        1966 Nov 14 -- autograph letter signed, card [flowers]
      - American Composers Alliance (Box 16, Folder 190)
        1966 Nov 28 -- typed letter signed
        1966 Nov 14 -- telegram
      - Ames, Elizabeth (Box 16, Folder 190)
        1966 Nov 14 -- autograph letter signed
      - Anderson, T.J., Jr. (Box 16, Folder 190)
        1966 Nov 20 -- autograph letter signed
      - Angell, Kay (Box 16, Folder 190)
        1966 Dec 12 -- autograph letter signed
      - Apgar, Virginia (Box 16, Folder 190)
        1966 Nov 17 -- autograph letter signed
      - Archer, Violet (Box 16, Folder 190)
      - Awes, William (Box 16, Folder 190)
        1966 Dec 17 -- autograph letter signed
      - Bacon, Ernst (Box 16, Folder 190)
        1966 Dec 30 -- autograph letter signed
      - Bahlman, Dudley (Box 16, Folder 190)
        [1966] -- autograph letter signed
      - Bailey, Parker (Box 16, Folder 190)
      - Bainton, Roland (Box 16, Folder 190)
        1966 Nov 16 -- autograph letter signed
      - Baird, Jim (Box 16, Folder 190)
        1966 Nov 21 -- autograph letter signed
      - Baisley, Robert (Box 16, Folder 190)
        1966 Nov 30 -- autograph letter signed
      - Baldwin, Sherman (Box 16, Folder 190)
        1966 Nov 15 -- autograph letter signed
      - Ballantine, Edward (Box 16, Folder 190)
      - Ballou, Esther Williamson (Box 16, Folder 190)
      - Bartholomew, Marshall (Box 16, Folder 190)
      - Bassett, Betty (Mrs. Charles) (Box 16, Folder 190)
        1966 Nov 28 -- autograph letter signed
      - Baumgartner, Hope Leroy (Box 16, Folder 190)
      - Beck, Sydney and Blanche (Box 16, Folder 191)
      - Beirne, Anna (Box 16, Folder 191)
        [1966] -- card
      - Bennett, Frances and Bill (Box 16, Folder 191)
      - Bennett, Robert Russell (Box 16, Folder 191)
      - Bergsma, William and Nickie (Box 16, Folder 191)
        1966 Nov 13 -- telegram
      - Berman, Gertrude and Harry (Box 16, Folder 191)
      - Bevan, Mary (Mrs. Frank) (Box 16, Folder 191)
      - Bevin, Florence (Box 16, Folder 191)
        1966 Nov 13 -- autograph letter signed
      - Blake, Al and Margaret (Box 16, Folder 191)
      - Blum, John (Box 16, Folder 191)
      - Blum, Pam (Box 16, Folder 191)
      - Boatwright, Alice (Box 16, Folder 191)
      - Boorsch, Louise and Jean (Box 16, Folder 191)
      - Bourret, Evelyn (Mrs. Clyde) (Box 16, Folder 191)
      - Boyle, Gay (Box 16, Folder 191)
        [19661 -- autograph letter signed
      - Bozyan, Margaret (Box 16, Folder 191)
      - Brewster, Kingman and Mary Louise (Box 16, Folder 192)
        card [flowers]
      - Bridges, L. Natalia R. (Box 16, Folder 192)
        1966 Nov 29 -- autograph letter signed
      - Broadcast Music, Inc. (Box 16, Folder 192)
      - Brodhead, Richard C. (Box 16, Folder 192)
      - Brombert, Mr. and Mrs. Victor (Box 16, Folder 192)
      - Browning, James (Box 16, Folder 192)
      - Buck, Polly (Box 16, Folder 192)
        1966 Nov 18 -- autograph letter signed
      - Burr, Ralph and Nipper (Box 16, Folder 192)
      - Campbell, Edith (Box 16, Folder 192)
      - Canfield, Kitty (Box 16, Folder 192)
      - Cannon, Beekman and Margaret (Box 16, Folder 192)
      - Cantlin, Sally (Box 16, Folder 192)
      - Carr, Christiana C. (Mrs. John W.) (Box 16, Folder 192)
      - Carrington, Edyth and Gordon (Box 16, Folder 192)
      - Catlin, Tod and Ni (Box 16, Folder 192)
      - Chadwick, Ahdel (Box 16, Folder 193)
        1967 Nov 12 -- autograph letter signed
      - Chaloff, Carol (Box 16, Folder 193)
      - Childs, Lois (Box 16, Folder 193)
      - Chisholm, Dugald (Box 16, Folder 193)
      - Claflin, Avery (Box 16, Folder 193)
      - Clarke, Hans T. (Box 16, Folder 193)
        1966 Nov 23 -- autograph letter signed
      - Clarke, Henry Leland and Julia (Box 16, Folder 193)
        1966 Nov 25 -- autograph letter signed
      - Closson, Heinie (Box 16, Folder 193)
        1966 Nov 19 -- autograph letter signed
      - Closson, Millie and David (Box 16, Folder 193)
      - Coeller, Mary (Box 16, Folder 193)
      - Coffin, Catherine (Mrs. William Sloane) (Box 16, Folder 193)
      - Cogswell, Connie (Box 16, Folder 193)
      - Collins, Barrie (Mrs. Stephen) (Box 16, Folder 193)
      - [Collinson, Noyer ?] (Box 16, Folder 193)
        1966 Nov 15 -- typed letter signed
      - Composers Recordings, Inc. (Box 16, Folder 193)
      - Cone, Edward T. (Box 16, Folder 193)
      - Connolly, Justin (Box 16, Folder 193)
        1966 Nov 14 -- typed letter signed
      - Contiguglia, John and Richard (Box 16, Folder 193)
      - Cooke, Brian (Box 16, Folder 193)
        1966 Dec 19 -- typed letter signed
      - Cooke, Lal (Box 16, Folder 193)
        1966 Nov 24 -- autograph letter signed
      - Cooper, Henry S.F., Jr. (Box 16, Folder 193)
      - Copland, Aaron (Box 16, Folder 194)
      - Copp, Mary (Mrs. Joseph Addison) (Box 16, Folder 194)
      - Corbin, Jane and Hale (Box 16, Folder 194)
      - Corey, Kay and Walter (Box 16, Folder 194)
      - Corwin, Margaret T. (Box 16, Folder 194)
      - Cottrell, Annette (Mrs. George W.) (Box 16, Folder 194)
      - Cowell, Sidney (Mrs. Henry) (Box 16, Folder 194)
        1966 Nov 14 -- card
      - Cowles, Mabel (Box 16, Folder 194)
      - Cowles, Phil (Box 16, Folder 194)
        1967 Feb 21 -- autograph letter signed
      - Cowley, Malcolm and Muriel (Box 16, Folder 194)
        1966 Nov 22 -- autograph letter signed
      - Crawford, Constance (Box 16, Folder 194)
      - Crena de Jongh, Polly (Box 16, Folder 194)
      - Crosby, Sumner (Box 16, Folder 194)
      - Crosby, Mr. and Mrs. Sumner (Box 16, Folder 194)
      - Crowley, John J. (Box 16, Folder 194)
      - Cumberland College (Box 16, Folder 194)
        1966 Nov 15 -- telegram
      - Currier, Donald (Box 16, Folder 195)
      - Curtis, Lewis P. (Box 16, Folder 195)
        1966 Nov 20 -- typed letter signed
      - Curtis, Alison (Mrs. Lewis P., Jr.) (Box 16, Folder 195)
      - Dana, Richard (Box 16, Folder 195)
      - Daniel, Oliver (Box 16, Folder 195)
      - D'Arms, Crit (Mrs. Edward F.) (Box 16, Folder 195)
      - D'Arms, Edward F. (Box 16, Folder 195)
      - D'Arms, Ted and Ellie (Box 16, Folder 195)
      - Davenny, Ward (Box 16, Folder 195)
      - Dean, Virginia (Box 16, Folder 195)
      - De Loache, Benjamin P. (Box 16, Folder 195)
      - De Loache, Mrs. Benjamin P. (Box 16, Folder 195)
      - De Mayo, Tony (Box 16, Folder 195)
      - De Vane, Mabel (Box 16, Folder 195)
      - Diamond, David (Box 16, Folder 195)
      - Diers, Ann (Mrs. H. Harmon) (Box 16, Folder 195)
      - Dobris, Joel C. (Box 16, Folder 196)
      - Doktor, Paul (Box 16, Folder 196)
        1966 Dec 27 -- autograph letter signed
      - Donaldson, Harry N. (Box 16, Folder 196)
        1966 Dec 7 -- autograph letter signed
      - Donaldson, Midge (Box 16, Folder 196)
      - Donnelley, Strachan (Box 16, Folder 196)
      - Dowds, Curt (Box 16, Folder 196)
      - Dresden, William (Box 16, Folder 196)
        1966 Nov.30 -- autograph letter signed
      - Driscoll, Rose and David (Box 16, Folder 196)
        1966 Dec 6 -- autograph letter signed
      - Dunham, William (Box 16, Folder 196)
      - Eberhart, Richard (Box 16, Folder 196)
        1967 Jan 13 -- typed letter signed
      - Eberle, Bruce H. (Box 16, Folder 196)